ASHWANI GUPTA

Frontend Developer

Contact: +91 7651841968 | ashwanigupta1242@gmail.com

Leetcode | Github | Portfolio

SUMMARY:

Software Developer with expertise in Front-End web technologies and cross platform app development frameworks.

Technical Skills:

Languages: C / C++, Dart, C#, Python, Golang, Javascript.

Frontend: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Tailwind CSS, React.js, Framer Motion. **Flutter / Dart:** Cross-Platform App development using flutter, dart.

Others: Git, Github, Firebase, Unity, Figma.

Experience:

Internship: Data Structures And Algorithm - Python

YBI Foundation | Jul 2023 - Aug 2023 | Remote, India

- Completed a project in HandWritten Digital Prediction And Classification Analysis using python libraries such as numpy, pandas with Jupyter Notebook.
- Completed a project in Servo Prediction using Linear Regression using python libraries such as numpy, pandas with Jupyter Notebook.

Internship: Data Structures And Algorithm - Python

YBI Foundation | Jul 2023 - Aug 2023 | Remote, India

- Completed a project in HandWritten Digital Prediction And Classification Analysis using python libraries such as numpy, pandas with Jupyter Notebook.
- Completed a project in Servo Prediction using Linear Regression using python libraries such as numpy, pandas with Jupyter Notebook.

Projects:

{ Link } Expense tracker App | flutter - dart

This is a Firebase service base application which is used to track users expenses and income using Firebase and Blocs.

{ Link } Sushi Restaurant Website | Frontend Web Project

This project contains a Weather API from openweather.com which is used to show current weather and hourly weather forecasts.

{ Link } React Blog Site | React.js

This project is a blog website that uses React.js along with HTML, CSS and Javascript. You can post, delete and add blogs in this website.

{Link} Weather App | flutter - dart

This project contains a Weather API from openweather.com which is used to show current weather and hourly weather forecasts.

Education:

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY (IT) | SR INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT AND TECHNOLOGY

AKTU University | Aug 2020 - Present